realtypost.org 2013-06-05

# PRIVACY POLICY | REALTYPOST.ORG

We know that privacy of your personal information is important. Therefore, we enclose what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit realtypost.org, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Personal information collected on this website**

No personally-identifiable information is collected on this website automatically, from consumers that browse the website for information or use the opt-out service. The only personally-identifiable information collected on this website is gathered on our “Contact Us” page, where you can provide your name, email address and other types of personal information. We collect this information solely to respond to the comments that you send to us via that contact form.

**Anonymous information collected on this website**

We record anonymous data such as traffic logs, number of visits or clicks on a given page, pages viewed or links to our site. We use IP addresses and cookies for gathering website statistics. We also store IP addresses on our server in the event that our site becomes corrupted and it becomes necessary to discover the cause of this corruption. We aggregate this anonymous data as part of managing, maintaining and reporting on use of our website.

We may share this anonymous data with third parties for the limited purpose of reporting on use of our website, or to comply with the applicable law. We do not rent, sell or share any anonymous data collected on this website with third parties for their marketing purposes.

None of this anonymous data is linked to personally-identifiable information and we make no attempt to link IP addresses to the individuals who visit this site.

**Cookies and web beacons**

We use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site.

We might use third party advertisements on realtypost.org to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you use to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for different ad targeting purposes.

You may opt-out of those cookies at the appropriate vendor or ad network websites if they provide that capability, or try to opt-out of some, but not all of these cookies in one location, at the Network Advertising Initiative [opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**DoubleClick DART cookies**

We may also use DART cookies for ad serving. The DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads served on our website. When you visit our website and either view or click an ad, a cookie may be dropped on your browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help better serve and manage ads on our website and across the web. Use of the DART cookie enables Google and its partners to serve ads to you on your visit of our or other pages on the Internet. You may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the advertising [opt-out page](http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_ads.html). Also, you can opt-out of any third party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative [opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in your other programs. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

**Links**

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our website or the information or content contained therein. Often links to other websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our website.

Please remember that when you use a link to go from our website to another website, our privacy policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link on our website, is subject to that website’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

**Controlling your privacy**

Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms.

**Changes to our privacy policy**

As our services evolve this privacy policy may be revised to reflect those changes, where applicable. We therefore reserve the right to amend this privacy policy at any time, for any reason. Notice of such amendments will be posted as an updated privacy policy on this website, and an effective date will be indicated. Users are encouraged to check our site frequently to review the current privacy policy in effect.

**Disclaimer**

This website is presented for the purpose of disseminating information only. This website does not guarantee the accuracy, reliability, currency, completeness of any material contained on the site, including all personal information uploaded to the site by its users. Furthermore, this internet site will not be accountable for any legal liability that may arise from any material contained on this website or on any linked site. This website is not a substitute for independent professional advice and users should obtain any appropriate professional advice relevant to their particular circumstances. The material on this website may include the views or recommendations of third parties, which do not necessarily reflect the views of this website, or indicate its commitment to a particular course of action. If you believe that the content on this website infringes another’s copyright, contact us via our [contact form](http://realtypost.org/contact-us/).

**Contact us**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please feel free to contact us through our [contact form](http://realtypost.org/contact-us/).
